=Visage and Soul=
("The Unique Her"
Trilogy on Women's Relationships)
=Episode 22=
What are you trying to do?
You said your name was Ji Ran.
You said you were my ex-boyfriend.
You said you got close to me
because of Ye Xiaoduo.
Listen to me.
Don't rush to answer.
From this moment on,
don't lie to me anymore.
Can you promise me that?
ظآزThere's no point in keeping this upظآز
A promise is a promise.
If you can't keep it,
don't make it.
ظآزBeing with you won't lead anywhereظآز
Okay.
Pinky swear.
ظآزWe've long been stuck on each otherظآز
ظآزWhy don't you understand?ظآز
ظآزGo find your own simple happinessظآز
ظآزDon't come and destroy meظآز
ظآزMy life rotted away because of youظآز
ظآزWhy won't you leave?ظآز
ظآزI don't want to ask why anymoreظآز
ظآزDid you ever hurt me?ظآز
ظآزI regret not pushing you off the cliffظآز
ظآزOnly seeing you fallظآز
ظآزWould make me truly happyظآز
ظآزSomeday I'll come see you
with my luggageظآز
ظآزWatching you cry aloneظآز
ظآزWhile I travel away with a smileظآز
ظآزWithout a trace of emotionظآز
You said
not even the King of Hell
could break this promise.
How did you end up like this?
Where's Xiaoduo?
The Ye Xiaoduo you're looking for
is dead.
That's impossible.
I...
I pulled her out of the fire.
How could she be dead?
Where is she?
Tell me!
After that fire,
you lived, and she died.
How dare you come here
and making a scene?
Get out!
From this day on,
there is no more
Ye Xiaoduo left in this world.
To uncover the truth
about what happened three years ago,
I had no choice
but to look like Ji Ran.
Because in the eyes of the Qiao family,
this is the Qin Yu they knew.
I deliberately made sure
Qiao Zhiwei could find me.
Unbelievable.
You look exactly like him.
To get your signature
on the property transfer agreement,
he had me pretend to be Qin Yu
and get close to the amnesiac you.
No one knows
what really happened that day.
Some people even said
you and Ji Ran set the fire.
I couldn't let you two
carry that stigma after you were gone.
ظآزWe say good morning, we say good nightظآز
ظآزWe say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurtظآز
ظآزThe sweeter it is, the luckier we seemظآز
ظآزYet the more romantic,
the rougher the roadظآز
ظآزLet me go, set me freeظآز
ظآزLet me drown in reckless silenceظآز
ظآزWe were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted itظآز
ظآزYou started
those ambiguous conversationsظآز
ظآزYet made me finish themظآز
ظآزLeading me like a moth to a flameظآز
ظآزStop joking and guessingظآز
ظآزAbout the choice I took most seriouslyظآز
ظآزNo matter how beautiful time is,
it still slips awayظآز
ظآزThe freedom you gave meظآز
ظآزBecame the heaviest chain I bearظآز
ظآزLove can barely move forwardظآز
You dummy.
ظآزYet the words still linger unspokenظآز
ظآزThe closeness I long forظآز
ظآزThere's no need for you
to keep avoiding itظآز
ظآزDon't break freeظآز
ظآزThank you for these chains
called freedomظآز
That was quick.
It's only been a few days,
and you've already set a wedding date.
Everything just fell into place.
Because we're truly in love.
True love?
Qin Yu.
You're really the perfect leading man.
Once she signs,
your role is over.
Sorry.
I'm already done here.
What do you mean?
She said
as long as my love for her is real,
nothing from the past matters.
So,
I'll be your brother-in-law now.
And you,
you're still
the Qiao family's loser.
What did you say?
I said you're loser.
You don't actually think
you're Qin Yu, do you?
Qiao Zhiwei,
she knows everything now.
Knows what?
It doesn't matter.
She loves me.
I forgot.
You wouldn't understand.
No one's ever loved you.
Love?
Let's see just how much she loves you.
ظآزWe say good morning, we say good nightظآز
ظآزWe say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurtظآز
ظآزThe sweeter it is, the luckier we seemظآز
ظآزYet the more romantic,
the rougher the roadظآز
ظآزLet me go, set me freeظآز
ظآزLet me drown in reckless silenceظآز
ظآزWe were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted itظآز
ظآزThe freedom you gave meظآز
ظآزBecame the heaviest chain I bearظآز
ظآزLove can barely move forwardظآز
ظآزYet the words still linger unspokenظآز
ظآزThe closeness I long forظآز
ظآزThere's no need for you
to keep avoiding itظآز
ظآزI don't want to break freeظآز
ظآزTake back the chains
disguised as freedomظآز